gone-hollywood.com 2014-06-28

# Privacy

This privacy statement covers all of the OTB Media network of sites (Outside the Beltway, [OTB Sports](http://sports.outsidethebeltway.com/), [Gone Hollywood](http://gone-hollywood.com/), and [Manzine](http://manzine.org/)). Please read this statement carefully before using proceeding to access OTB Media sites. Your use of OTB Media indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

**Resale or disclosure of information to third parties** : OTB Media does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or email lists.

**Information Collection** : OTB Media may collect information from our users at several different points.

**Comments** : In order to enhance their use of the OTB Media sites, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. To leave a comment, users must submit information including an email address. OTB Media may use this, and other information, to screen out users who leave comments prohibited by our terms and conditions of use, and will not pass this information to any other organization.

**Mailing List** : OTB Media may launch a mailing list for some or all of the member sites. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list. All mailing lists will have an easily located “unsubscribe” option.

**Cookies** : A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

By setting a cookie on an OTB Media site, users will not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on the site’s discussion board. We store a cookie on each user’s machine that contains a username and encrypted password. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Wizbang Online products or services that require you to “sign in,” and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings.

**Third Party Cookies** : Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, Wizbang Online has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by OTB Media only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third Party Advertising** : The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by BlogAds, Tacoda, Google, among other services. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. For more information about Google and cookies, please click here.

**Log Files** : Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer** : Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, OTB Media may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of the the OTB Network sites.

**Links** : OTB Media contains links to other sites. Please be aware that OTB Media is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Wizbang Online.

**Notification of Changes** : Whenever OTB Media changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
